Guide to the Gail and Stephen Rudin American presidential collection, 1775-2009.
Rudin, Gail and Stephen American presidential collection
- Series II. Other U.S. presidents
  - Monroe, James Office held: As Secy of State Writer's location: Washington, D.C., August 28, 1812; Pages: 1, framed (Box 5, Folder 27)
    Additional instructions to the public and private armed vessels of the United States.
    Rudin # P-124
  - Monroe, James Office held: As President Addressee: John Gates Writer's location: Washington, D.C., November 27, 1817; Pages: 1 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    Land grant rewarded to Private John Gates.
    Rudin # P-125
  - Monroe, James, 1954, 1958; Stamps (Box 5, Folder 28)
    Commemorative envelopes with 5-cent stamps and 3-cent stamps.
  - Nixon, Richard, Stamps (Box 5, Folder 29)
    Commemorative and memorial envelopes and stamps.
  - Nixon, Richard Office held: As Lieutenant Commander, U.S. Navy Addressee: "Roy O. Day - Chairman 12th Congressional District" Writer's location: Middle River, Maryland, November 29, 1945; Pages: 1 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    Prepares for his run for public office.
    Rudin # P-126
  - Nixon, Richard Office held: As Vice President Addressee: Robert K. Pepper - News Editor, Fort Meyers News Press Writer's location: Washington, D.C., May 14, 1957; Pages: 2 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Discusses how to handle Russia. See Lyndon Johnson letter of 7/22/57, also written to Mr. Pepper.
    Rudin # P-127
  - Nixon, Richard Office held: As candidate for Governor of California Addressee: Congressman Bob Wilson Writer's location:, May 14, 1962; Pages: 1 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Proper governance demands "political leaders of absolute probity and judgement".
    Rudin # P-128
  - Nixon, Richard Office held: As Lawyer Addressee: Jimmy Bottoms Writer's location: New York, NY, February 3, 1964; Pages: 2 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Discusses the office of the Vice Presidency.
    Rudin # P-129
  - Nixon, Richard Office held: As President? Writer's location: Washington, D.C., January 20, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Inauguration Envelope.
    Rudin # P-130
  - Nixon, Richard Office held: As President Addressee: Senator Jennings Randolph Writer's location: "The White House Washington, D.C.", April 11, 1970; Pages: 1 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Regarding Carswell appointment to the Supreme Court.
    Rudin # P-131
  - Nixon, Richard Office held: As President Writer's location: Washington, D.C., 1974 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Official printed ticket to impeachment.
    Rudin # P-132
  - Nixon, Richard Office held: As President Addressee: Congressman Albert H. Quie Writer's location: "The White House Washington, D.C.", February 20, 1974; Pages: 1 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Regarding resigning the Presidency.
    Rudin # P-133
  - Nixon, Richard Office held: As Presidential candidate Writer's location:, August 9, 1974; Pages: 1 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Announcing Nixon's resignation and Ford's ascension to office.
    Rudin # P-134
  - Nixon, Richard, August 9, 1974; Newspaper (Box 13, Folder 7)
    The New York Times coverage of Nixon's resignation.
  - Nixon, Richard Office held: As ex-President Writer's location: New York, NY, 1985
    "No More Vietnams". Signed copy. Arbor House, New York. Also included is an unsigned copy. See separated material below.
    Rudin # P-135
  - Nixon, Richard Office held: As ex-President Addressee: Lee Edwards Writer's location: New York, NY, February 22, 1985; Pages: 1 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Review the American role in Vietnam.
    Rudin # P-136
  - Nixon, Richard Office held: As ex-President Addressee: Senator Paul Simon Writer's location: New York, NY, August 16, 1985; Pages: 1 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Regarding exchange programs with Russia.
    Rudin # P-137
  - Nixon, Richard Office held: No elective office held Addressee: Patrick J. Hillings Writer's location: New York City, January 26, 1988; Pages: 1 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Contains commentary about the media and "beating them".
  - Nixon, Richard Office held: As ex-President Addressee: Senator Daniel Patrick Moynihan Writer's location: Woodcliff Lake, NJ, August 16, 1990; Pages: 2 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    Discusses race relations.
    Rudin # P-138
  - Nixon, Richard, April 23, 1994; Newspaper (Box 13, Folder 10)
    New York Times coverage of Nixon's death.
  - Obama, Barack, Stamps (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Commemorative envelopes with 42-cent stamps, foreign stamps, inaugural covers, and note cards with stamps.
  - Obama, Barack Office held: Addressee: Writer's location: "Crown Publishers New York, NY", 2006
    "The Audacity of Hope". See separated material below.
    Rudin # P-138A
  - Obama, Barack, 2009; Newspaper (Box 11)
    The New York Times special publication of inaugurations, from Washington to Obama.
    Rudin # N-16
  - Obama, Barack, 2008-2009; Newspapers (Box 20)
    Four newspapers/magazines on the election and inauguration.
  - Obama, Barack, November 5, 2008 (Box 21)
    Press plate announcing Obama's win.
  - Pierce, Franklin Office held: As Congressman Addressee: Pierce's Father Writer's location: Washington, D.C., December 23, 1835; Pages: 3 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    Concerning his attention to religious service, public and private. Pierce's letter is a continuation of a letter written by his brother, also to their father.
    Rudin # P-139
  - Pierce, Franklin Office held: As Brigadier General Addressee: Endorses letter of Lt. Col. Joshua Howard Writer's location: Chapultepec, Mexico, September 26, 1847; Pages: 3 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    Howard's letter recommends promotions and Certificates of Merit for bravery following the Battle of Churubusco and Chapultepec.
    Rudin # P-140
  - Pierce, Franklin Office held: As President Writer's location: Washington, D.C., June 2, 1856; Pages: 1 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    Proclamation concerning the boundary between the United States and Mexico.
    Rudin # P-141
  - Polk, James Office held: As President Writer's location: Washington, D.C., December 26, 1848; Pages: 1, framed (Box 6, Folder 17)
    Orders that the battle flags captured during the Mexican War be deposited at West Point.
    Rudin # P-142
  - Reagan, Ronald, Stamps (Box 6, Folder 18)
    Commemorative envelopes and stamps.
  - Reagan, Ronald Office held: Probably as Governor of California Addressee: Tom Reed, Pages: 1 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    Thinks U.S. foreign policy should be "a little hard nosed".
    Rudin # P-143
  - Reagan, Ronald Office held: As Governor of California Addressee: Sgt. Ernie A. Siegrist Writer's location: Sacramento, CA, June 28, 1967; Pages: 2 1/2 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    Response to an angry serviceman in Vietnam.
    Rudin # P-144
  - Reagan, Ronald Office held: As Governor of California Addressee: George F. Barrett Writer's location: Sacramento, CA, October 13, 1967; Pages: 1 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    Returns a campaign contribution.
    Rudin # P-145
  - Reagan, Ronald Office held: As Governor of California Addressee: Mike Fitchett Writer's location: Sacramento, CA, August 5, 1969; Pages: 1 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    Comments on the reform of the Electoral College.
    Rudin # P-146
  - Reagan, Ronald Office held: As Governor of California Addressee: Mrs. Donald S. Bolton Writer's location: Sacramento, CA, January 4, 1971; Pages: 1 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    Discusses tax relief.
    Rudin # P-147
  - Reagan, Ronald Office held: As ex-Governor of California Addressee: Lloyd E. Rohrke Writer's location: Los Angeles, CA, June 9, 1975; Pages: 1 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    Has soured on being a legislator. "anyway it's not for me."
    Rudin # P-148
  - Reagan, Ronald Office held: As ex-President Addressee: The Honorable and Mrs. James Brady Writer's location: (Likely California), November 24, 1993; Pages: 1 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    Congratulations on the passage of the Brady Bill.
    Rudin # P-149
  - Roosevelt, Franklin, Stamps (Box 6, Folder 26)
    Commemorative envelopes and stamps
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Office held: No public office held Addressee: Mrs. Teresa Graham Writer's location: Hyde Park, NY, December 4, 1924; Pages: 2 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    Outlines his plan for strengthening the Democratic Party.
    Rudin # P-150
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Office held: As Governor of New York Addressee: Mrs. C.F. Wertz Writer's location: Albany, NY, February 3, 1930; Pages: 1 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    The definition of ideal citizenship.
    Rudin # P-151
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Office held: As Governor of New York Addressee: Mr. H.S. Wellman Writer's location: Albany, NY, January 14, 1931; Pages: 1 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    Regarding the Patients Aid Fund at the Georgia Warm Springs Foundation. From the Dr. Joseph Plaud Collection.
    Rudin # P-152
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Office held: As Governor of New York Addressee: Walter L. Bennett Writer's location: Albany, NY, February 15, 1932; Pages: 1 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Response to a detractor.
    Rudin # P-152A
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Office held: As Governor of New York Addressee: Lewis A. Lincoln Writer's location: Albany, NY, February 19, 1932; Pages: 1 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    I am a Democrat "by conviction".
    Rudin # P-153
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Office held: As Governor of New York Addressee: Mr. W.F. Bussell Writer's location: Albany, NY, February 26, 1932; Pages: 1 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Regarding the Square Deal, Democratic Principles, and the suffering American people.
    Rudin # P-154
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Office held: President, March 4, 1933 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    Program for the Inaugural Ceremonies.
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Office held: As President Addressee: "George Creel, Colliers Magazine" Writer's location: "The White House Washington, D.C.", September 19, 1935; Pages: 1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    An early trial balloon in FDR's battle against the Supreme Court. See also FDR letter of 12/18/36.
    Rudin # P-155
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Office held: As President Addressee: Basil O'Connor Writer's location: "The White House Washington, D.C.", November 16, 1936; Pages: 1 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    "The national fight against Infantile Paralysis cannot cease. It must go on!"
    Rudin # P-156
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Office held: As President Addressee: "Samuel I. Rosenman, Roosevelt's Speech Writer" Writer's location: On U.S.S. Indianapolis, December 10, 1936; Pages: 1 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    FDR misses Rosenman's speech writing expertise.
    Rudin # P-157
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Office held: As President Addressee: Basil O'Connor Writer's location: "The White House Washington, D.C.", December 18, 1936; Pages: 1 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Prepares to manipulate the press. See also FDR letter of 9/19/35.
    Rudin # P-158
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Office held: As President Addressee: "Norman Thomas, Socialist Party Leader" Writer's location: "The White House Washington, D.C.", December 25, 1937; Pages: 3 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Regarding the export of arms to Spain during the Spanish Civil War.
    Rudin # P-159
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Office held: As President Addressee: William S. Paley, President, Columbia Broadcasting System Writer's location: "The White House Washington, D.C.", April 22, 1938; Pages: 1 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    FDR praises Paley for keeping the radio airwaves open for public and political discussions.
    Rudin # P-160
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Office held: As President Addressee: Gutzon Borglum Writer's location: "The White House Washington, D.C.", May 19, 1938; Pages: 1 (Box 7, Folder 6a)
    Roosevelt writes to Gutzon Borglum, sculptor of Mount Rushmore, concerning the Monument's creation and funding.
    Rudin # P-160AA
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Office held: As President Addressee: Heads of All Departments and Independent Establishments Writer's location: "The White House Washington, D.C.", September 3, 1941; Pages: 1 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Directive relating to the employment of negroes in the Federal Civil Service.
    Rudin # P-160A
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Office held: As President Addressee: Martin C. Sweeney Writer's location: "The White House Washington, D.C.", October 19, 1943; Pages: 1 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    FDR sends sly thanks for a gift of liquor.
    Rudin # P-161
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Office held: As President Addressee: Dr. Harry L. Hopkins Writer's location: Warm Springs, GA, December 8, 1944; Pages: 1 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    FDR pokes fun at Thomas Dewey's mustache. From the Dr. Joseph Plaud Collection.
    Rudin # P-162
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Office held: As President Addressee: Edwin B. Wilson Writer's location: "The White House Washington, D.C.", April 4, 1945; Pages: 2 (Box 7, Folder 9a)
    Eight days prior to his death, Roosevelt sends greetings to All Souls Universalist Church, Brooklyn. He then states, "not one of the least of our cherished freedoms is freedom of conscience. It is a cornerstone of our national happiness -- a freedom which we are now defending and shall always defend as a bullwork of democracy and civilization."
    Also includes letter from Matthew Connelly to Cornelius Greenway, Acknowledgement of Greenway's letter of April 21, 1945, probably requesting a message from the President, which had already been sent before Roosevelt's death (dated April 27, 1945).
    Rudin # P-163
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Office held: As deceased President Writer's location:, April 13, 1945; Pages: 1 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Official naval teletype announcing death of FDR.
    Rudin # P-164
  - Roosevelt, Franklin, 1845; Newspaper (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Philadelphia Inquirer coverage of Roosevelt's death and Truman's oath.
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, Stamps (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Commemorative stamps and envelopes.
  - Roosevelt, Theodore Office held: As President Addressee: "Honorable Morris K. Jessup, President, Chamber of Commerce State of New York" Writer's location: "Executive Mansion Washington, D.C.", October 15, 1901; Pages: 1 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    Declines to speak at the Chamber of Commerce "until my message goes before Congress".
    Rudin # P-165
  - Roosevelt, Theodore Office held: As ex-President Addressee: "Mr. O.K. Davis, New York Times" Writer's location: """The Outlook"" New York, NY", May 31, 1911; Pages: 1 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    "No situation could arise which would make it possible for me to accept a nomination next year". See also letter of 12/14/1911 - from the Forbes Collection - Part 6.
    Rudin # P-166
  - Roosevelt, Theodore Office held: As ex-President Writer's location: New York, NY, October 10, 1911; Pages: 1 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    Made out to Harvard Alumni Association.
    Rudin # P-167
  - Roosevelt, Theodore Office held: As ex-President Addressee: J.M. Hummel Writer's location: """The Outlook"" New York, NY", December 14, 1911; Pages: 1 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    "I do not want to be nominated for any office". See also letter of 5/31/1911.
    Rudin # P-168
  - Roosevelt, Theodore Office held: As ex-President about to be nominated by the new Progressive Party Addressee: Lady Gregory Writer's location: New York, NY, July 2, 1912; Pages: 1 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    Discusses his feelings as Progressive candidate in the 1912 presidential election. Included is a TLS (secretarially signed) dated 10/19/1912. From the hospital, Roosevelt mentions campaigning and the unsuccessful assassination attempt on his life.
    Rudin # P-169
  - Roosevelt, Theodore Office held: As ex-President Addressee: "Dr. Henry Waldo Coe, Senator from Oregon" Writer's location: New York, NY, November 7, 1914; Pages: 1 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    "The public at large had gotten tired of all of us reformers and especially of me".
    Rudin # P-170
  - Taft, William H. Office held: As President Writer's location:, August 22, 1911; Pages: 24 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Archive consisting of two drafts of Taft's "Special Message of the President of the United States, Returning Without Approval House Bill No. 12812. An Act to reduce the duties on Manufacture of Cotton".
    Rudin # P-171
  - Taft, William H. Addressee: Walter Smith Writer's location: Washington, DC., November 9, 1912; Pages: 1 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    Taft discusses his loss to Woodrow Wilson in the 1912 election.
  - Taft, William H. Office held: "As ex-President and Professor of Law, Yale University" Addressee: S.G. Bayne Writer's location: New Haven, CT, September 20, 1913; Pages: 1 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    Discusses losing some of his weight.
    Rudin # P-172
  - Taft, William H. Office held: As ex-President and Joint Chairman of the National War Labor Board Addressee: "Clarence H. Kelsey, President, Title Guarantee and Trust Co." Writer's location: Pointe-au-Pic, Quebec, Canada, August 4, 1918; Pages: 1 1/2 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    Sees a long war continuing, discusses Russia and Germany, calls for a larger American draft.
    Rudin # P-173
  - Taft, William H. Office held: "As ex-President and Professor of Law, Yale University" Addressee: "Dudley E. Waters, President Grand Rapids Bank" Writer's location: New Haven, CT, November 17, 1919; Pages: 1 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    Discusses sound education and the formation of educational funds.
    Rudin # P-174
  - Taft, William H. Office held: As ex-President and Chief Justice of the United States Addressee: "Clarence H. Kelsey, President, Title Guarantee and Trust Co." Writer's location: Washington, D.C., October 6, 1922; Pages: 1 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    Regarding his High Court colleagues.
    Rudin # P-175
  - Taft, William H. Office held: As ex-President and Chief Justice of the United States Addressee: Honorable Charles G. Washburn Writer's location: Pointe-au-Pic Quebec, Canada, September 23, 1927; Pages: 2 1/2 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    Acknowledges his 70th birthday; discusses what he would like to do in his remaining years.
    Rudin # P-176
  - Taylor, Zachary Office held: As Major General Writer's location:, 1846; During Mexican War; Pages: 1
    Part of a Pay Voucher including servants.
    Moved to the Gail and Stephen Rudin Slavery Collection, collection #4681.
    Rudin # P-177
  - Taylor, Zachary Office held: As Major General Addressee: Mr. S.C. Holden Writer's location: Camp near Monterray, Mexico, June 29, 1847; Pages: 1 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    Citizens of Batavia, NY endorse Taylor for President. He says that there are much better men than himself who are qualified. With newspaper article.
    Rudin # P-178
  - Truman, Harry, Stamps (Box 7, Folder 25)
    Envelope with stamps.
  - Truman, Harry Office held: As President Addressee: Senator Walter F. George Writer's location: "The White House Washington, D.C.", August 25, 1945; Pages: 1 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    Reviews troop redeployment at war's end.
    Rudin # P-179
  - Truman, Harry, 1848; Newspaper (Box 13, Folder 5)
    Chicago Daily Tribune of the election.
  - Truman, Harry Office held: As President Addressee: David H. Morgan Writer's location: "The White House Washington, D.C.", July 16, 1948; Pages: 1 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    Ridicules the hypocritical Republican platform.
    Rudin # P-180
  - Truman, Harry Office held: As President Writer's location: "Cabinet Room The White House Washington, D.C.", August 12, 1948; Pages: 2 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    Authorizing loan for construction of U.N. Headquarters in N.Y. City.
    Rudin # P-181
  - Truman, Harry Office held: As President Addressee: Wilbur J. Abell Writer's location: "The White House Washington, D.C.", April 4, 1950; Pages: 1 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    "We have tried to arrange things so that (Margaret) would attain that success on merit".
    Rudin # P-182
  - Truman, Harry Office held: As President Addressee: "Barney Nover The Denver Post" Writer's location: "The White House Washington, D.C.", November 4, 1950; Pages: 1 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    Refers to his attempted assassination.
    Rudin # P-183
  - Truman, Harry Office held: As President Addressee: Edward D. McKim Writer's location: "The White House Washington, D.C.", April 14, 1951; Pages: 1 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    On the firing of MacArthur. From the Forbes Collection - Part Six.
    Rudin # P-184
  - Truman, Harry Office held: As ex-President Addressee: Paul V. Lutz Writer's location: Independence, Missouri, June 22, 1959; Pages: 1 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    Former Presidents are discarded.
    Rudin # P-185
  - Truman, Harry Office held: As ex-President Addressee: Winston Norman Writer's location: Independence, Missouri, January 1960; Pages: 1 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    Says "No" to running for President in 1960. Included is a copy of a letter from Norman to Truman (1/8/1950) asking him to accept the Presidential nomination. Envelope of Truman letter has a printed Free Frank signature.
    Rudin # P-186
  - Truman, Harry Office held: As ex-President Addressee: Honorable Leonor K. Sullivan Writer's location: Independence, Missouri, October 5, 1960; Pages: 1 1/2 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    Vigorously campaigns for the Democratic Presidential ticket of John Kennedy and Lyndon Johnson.
    Rudin # P-187
  - Truman, Harry Office held: As ex-President Addressee: Edmund G. Brown, Governor, California Writer's location: Independence, Missouri, October 19, 1966; Pages: 2 (Box 7, Folder 34a)
    Truman comments on the political wisdom of the American people. Also includes unsigned copy of another letter to Truman from Brown, "I lost, but your letter was of tremendous help. I should have had the sense you had and not run for a third term"...
    Rudin # P-188
  - Truman, Harry Office held: As ex-President Addressee: Robert Lovett Writer's location: Independence, Missouri, August 5, 1970; Pages: 1 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    How a teacher should communicate with students. Envelope has printed Free Frank Signature.
    Rudin # P-189
  - Truman, Harry Office held: As ex-President Addressee: Miss. Maria Smith Writer's location: Independence, Missouri, December 9, 1970; Pages: 1 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Explains the "S" in his name. Envelope has printed Free Frank Signature.
    Rudin # P-190
  - Tyler, John Office held: As President Writer's location:, November 10, 1841; Pages: 1 (Box 8, Folder 1A)
    Four Language Sea Letter for the Bark "Elizabeth" for a whaling voyage.
    Rudin # P-191
  - Tyler, John Office held: As ex-President Addressee: Robert Tyler (his son) Writer's location: Sherwood Forest, January 19, 1849; Pages: 1 1/2 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Mourns the loss of his grandson to cholera.
    Rudin # P-192
  - Van Buren, Martin Office held: As Secretary of State Writer's location: Washington, D.C., July 13, 1829; Pages: 1 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Certificate of Copyright for the book "Sketches of Naval Life".
    Rudin # P-193
  - Van Buren, Martin Office held: As Vice President Addressee: William C. Rives Writer's location: Washington, D.C., February 14, 1836; Pages: 2 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Reports on diplomatic affairs involving France and Great Britain.
    Rudin # P-194
  - Van Buren, Martin Office held: As ex-President Addressee: Henry D. Gilpin Writer's location: Lindenwald, June 10, 1856; Pages: 4 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Political letter on the 1856 Presidential Election, Van Buren's relationship with James Buchanan, and the Democratic Party's chances in New York State.
    Rudin # P-195
  - Washington, George, 1939, 1982; Stamps (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Commemorative stamps.
  - Washington, George Office held: As ex-Commander of the Continental Army Addressee: Colonel John Fitzpatrick Writer's location: Mount Vernon, November 26, 1785; Pages: 1 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    The toil of a legislator re: the Potomac Company. Not in "Writings" ed. J.C. Fitzpatrick.
    Rudin # P-196
  - Wilson, Woodrow Office held: "As Professor of Law and Politics, Princeton University" Addressee: Frank Walter Brooks Writer's location: "Judd Haven, Ontario, Canada", September 11, 1900; Pages: 3 (Box 8, Folder 7)